<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>insight on Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>/tags/insight/</link>
    <description>Recent content in insight on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tags/insight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Is programming an art or a craft?</title>
      <link>/blogs/programming/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/programming/programming/</guid>
      <description>Art can be faked, but the craft can’t. Well, this is true indeed. Any piece of art ever created is subjective, to make it more cheesy with modern day WhatsApp statuses, “Beauty lies in the eye of a beholder”. Art requires a sufficient amount of psychological operation to convince the value. Some artists are clever, they create on top of their precursors, it’s a safe bet. Some do create something very appealing to the masses, where they can relate themselves with them.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Art can be faked, but the craft can’t. Well, this is true indeed. Any piece of art ever created is subjective, to make it more cheesy with modern day WhatsApp statuses, “Beauty lies in the eye of a beholder”. Art requires a sufficient amount of psychological operation to convince the value. Some artists are clever, they create on top of their precursors, it’s a safe bet. Some do create something very appealing to the masses, where they can relate themselves with them. This happens because, most of the things that we see around were built upon a system by a small group of people who eventually convinced everyone what’s good for them. Art and historiography are no different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember that Steve Jobs once said, “Design is not just what it looks like and feels like. Design is how it works.” Well, that’s true. A frugal structure as shiny as Venus is not worth of love. With all these perceptions and interpretations, I have come to believe that, programming is a craft rather than an art. It could be romanticized as art, but seldom have some truth to it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at the history, there wasn’t much emphasis given to craftsman / craftswomen compared to artists. Even it’s true today. Dignity of labor can only be achieved if we pay attention to the work of craftspeople. Some Nordic countries have achieved this to some extent, but it’s an alien concept to many, or it has become hard for large economies to breakout off the complex system that they have created and try something different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The people who built Taj Mahal are unknown, the people who built Pyramids are unknown. So what have we got? Egos of historians, media, and politicians. Bygones are bygones, but I like it when Linus Torvalds says, “Talk is cheap and show me the code”. With my experience working with lathe machines and garage have always made me think about the precision and accuracy. Scientists do the same, crafts work, some are underrated and some are unsung heroes/heroines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But there’s also a dichotomy in this craft of someone being better, but I think the competition is healthy as the outcome of competitive craft is a better solution rather than a better subjective perspective, which in my opinion have already been said and told long back, and it keeps on reiterating as an old wine in the new bottle.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;With the rapid growth of technology, it has become a bit easier for people from any part of the world to learn and build things by the means of programming. Today, every craftsman/craftswomen is able to get their due credit, who could have their own creativity and own design. All thanks to open source and the culture that has been developed overtime. There are still some issues with psychological operations that go around reputation, but let’s hope it’ll be obsolete as we move forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The true ingenuity is when we write our own code. It’s a craft which can give wings to our creativity, artistic biases and solving the problem at hand. The advent of AI would probably solve or make it easier for the concerns that our left part of the brain had. Hopefully we’ll get some time to solve the problems of our right part of the brain. Or will we merge them together?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web 1.5</title>
      <link>/blogs/web-1.5/web-1.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/web-1.5/web-1.5/</guid>
      <description>What’s in a name? That which we call “Interactive web”, “Read-Write web” and some other names would serve a bit more for social media. Web 2.0 was a revolution in its own right. The window of opportunities and possibilities compounded after that, the present tech giants never looked back.
I really love tech forums, IRC channels, mailing lists and jabber chats. Especially the ones that are focused on STEM (in a broader sense), devoid of political opinions and subjective interpretations; just normal people discussing logical solutions to abiotic systems that could impact the masses.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;What’s in a name? That which we call “Interactive web”, “Read-Write web” and some other names would serve a bit more for social media. Web 2.0 was a revolution in its own right. The window of opportunities and possibilities compounded after that, the present tech giants never looked back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really love tech forums, IRC channels, mailing lists and jabber chats. Especially the ones that are focused on STEM (in a broader sense), devoid of political opinions and subjective interpretations; just normal people discussing logical solutions to abiotic systems that could impact the masses. Well, pardon me for the exaggeration there, I call the transition period from Web 1.0 to Web 2.0 and the communication systems which stayed relevant regardless of time as Web 1.5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interaction was missing on Web 1.0. As the world stepped into Web 2.0, the social media took over exponentially. A new category was formed, habits changed rapidly and innovations never came to a halt. But, if you think about that on a deeper level, it all happened in a not so secret, maybe a bit socially boring underground called Web 1.5; a strong driving force impacting millions without consultation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll try not to include entrepreneurship forums in the category of Web 1.5. Because business is a different ball game, and requires a different level of psychological operations. Now let’s talk about why Web 1.5 is crucial, and it’ll persist for some time. There are two main things that I can think of. Number one—old habits die hard. Since the advent of the web, most of the interactions are done similarly to what’s happening today on Discord or Slack, old wine in a new bottle or simply call it &amp;lsquo;culture&amp;rsquo;. Number two–some eerie virtual human connection. Who would have thought that real-time text-based interaction could become a powerful medium of communication?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Web 1.5 is everywhere, but at the same time nowhere or the majority of them would never care. Betterment is a hoax? Not fully, we are what we are. Will a major shift happen in the Metaverse? Partially, because not all things can be expressed in texts, AV or the virtual world.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
