<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>insight on Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>/tags/insight/</link>
    <description>Recent content in insight on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tags/insight/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Web 1.5</title>
      <link>/blogs/web-1.5/web-1.5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/web-1.5/web-1.5/</guid>
      <description>What’s in a name? That which we call “Interactive web”, “Read-Write web” and some other names would serve a bit more for social media. Web 2.0 was a revolution in its own right. The window of opportunities and possibilities compounded after that, the present tech giants never looked back.
I really love tech forums, IRC channels, mailing lists and jabber chats. The interaction that happens there is something refreshing, which, I’m sure, doesn’t make lots of money for the social media companies.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;What’s in a name? That which we call “Interactive web”, “Read-Write web” and some other names would serve a bit more for social media. Web 2.0 was a revolution in its own right. The window of opportunities and possibilities compounded after that, the present tech giants never looked back.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I really love tech forums, IRC channels, mailing lists and jabber chats. The interaction that happens there is something refreshing, which, I’m sure, doesn’t make lots of money for the social media companies. Besides tech, let’s think about the forums or social media platforms that are subject specific, especially focused on STEM (in a broader sense), devoid of political opinions and subjective interpretations; just human beings discussing logical solutions for abiotic systems that could impact biotic life. Well, pardon me for the exaggeration there, I call it Web 1.5.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Interaction was missing on Web 1.0. As the world stepped into Web 2.0, the social media took over exponentially. A new category was formed, habits changed rapidly and innovations never came to a halt. But, if you think about that on a deeper level, it all happened in a not so secret, maybe a bit socially boring underground called Web 1.5; the single driving force impacting millions without consultation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ll try not to include entrepreneurship forums in the category of Web 1.5. Because business is a different ball game, and requires a different level of psychological operations. Now let’s talk about why Web 1.5 is crucial, and it’ll persist for some time. There are two main things that I can think of. Number one—old habits die hard. Since the advent of the web, most of the interactions are done similarly to what’s happening today on Discord or Slack, old wine in a new bottle. Number two–some eerie virtual human connection. Who would have thought that real-time text-based interaction could become a powerful medium of communication?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, Web 1.5 is everywhere, but at the same time nowhere or the majority of them would never care. Betterment is a hoax? Not fully, we are what we are. Will a major shift happen in the Metaverse? Partially, because not all things cannot be expressed in texts, AV or the virtual world.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
