<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:48:04 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amoghavarsha.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Communities - The Good, The Bad and The Ugly</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/community/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:48:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/community/community/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Community: a group of people living in the same place or having a particular characteristic in common.&amp;rdquo;
It&amp;rsquo;s a fission reaction! If we consider the whole world as a giant community and start dividing it into subgroups, there would be millions of little groups. Some call it diversity, and some call it poles. Whatever it is, we live in some kind of community, knowingly or unknowingly.
Some communities we choose deliberately because they pique our interest, and some of them are just inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Facebook And Midnight Mass</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/midnight/midnight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 21:27:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/midnight/midnight/</guid>
      <description>I recently joined Facebook. It&amp;rsquo;s been some odd 6-7 years ago since I left the platform. The reason for rejoining Facebook is fairly simple - Communities. Well, the social media platform has been around for many years, and their penetration is massive. There are so many old tech, travel, food, entrepreneurship communities thriving on Facebook. Even though I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of doom scrolling, lately I&amp;rsquo;ve been active in programming communities and I am trying to answer the majority of questions there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arrays Are Powerful In Bash</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/aib/aib/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 19:34:01 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/aib/aib/</guid>
      <description>“$” might symbolize dollars to many of you, but for bash users it’s the holy grail for retrieving stored data. Speaking of which, do you know what’s the common place to store a piece of data? A variable.
Variable The name itself incurs that variable is something that could be varied. So is it like a chameleon that changes colors all the time? Not precisely, if you remember from the intro its a common place to store a piece of data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzing With Good Old Radamsa</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/radamsa/radamsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/radamsa/radamsa/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;1337051nT&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;S3rlockedOSINTForall&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;oS$INTFOR@LL&amp;rdquo;
Did you know that Osint For All has many secret domain names? Just kidding, I don’t want to fuzz around any further, or maybe I do? So let’s jump in to the world of Radamsa.
Radamsa is a fuzzer. In technical terms, it is a test case generator for robustness testing. Typically, it is used to test how well a program could tolerate potentially malicious input. It works by reading files of valid data and generating random outputs every time from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of mind-bending movies</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/non-linear/non-linear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/non-linear/non-linear/</guid>
      <description>Mind-bending/non-linear/mind-twisting movies have a special place in my heart. So here’s a list of some non-linear movies that I’ve watched, those of which I can remember.
Inception Interstellar Identity (2003) Mr.Nobody (2009) Mulholland Drive 2001: A Space Odyssey (1968) Memento (2000) Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004) Groundhog Day Black Swan (2010) Pi (1998) Shutter Island (2010) The Butterfly Effect (2004) Triangle (2009) Confessions (2010) [Japanese] Donnie Darko (2001) 3-Iron (2004) [Korean] Be With You (2018) [Korean] Fight Club The Man from Earth (2007) Source Code (2011) Birdman (2014) The Fountain (2006) Timecrimes (2007) [Spanish] Paprika (2006) [Anime] Mirage (2018) [Spanish] The Double (2013) Predestination (2014) Synecdoche, New York (2008) Primer (2004) Enemy (2013) Vanilla Sky (2001) Looper (2012) The Others (2001) Mother!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some favorite movies</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/movies/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/movies/movies/</guid>
      <description>I am a big movie buff. Since the day I started using the computer, before diving into the internals of the computer, I’ve spent a lot of time watching movies. Maybe that’s a fractal stain in almost all Indian Engineering colleges. Even now, I love to watch movies/TV shows like the rest.
Phase 1 I don’t exactly remember what was the first foreign film that I watched. Back then, I used to have a friend who gave me a lot of English movies, such as Inception (which I watched after five years), Fight Club (which I watched lethargically), Prestige (which I watched but didn’t remember).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steganographic Tools For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/steganography/steganography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/posts/steganography/steganography/</guid>
      <description>Hiding in plain sight has many dimensions. Sometimes, whatever you are looking for is before you, but you cannot see it; other times, it’s right before you but you don’t notice.
Steganography has been an art since the ancient days used to write hidden messages. It has evolved over the ages, and has changed form for the better. Nowadays we have software to hide and obfuscate messages. In this article, we’ll take a look at some amazing steganographic tools which are tiny yet powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Games</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/games/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/games/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Socials</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/socials/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/socials/</guid>
      <description>Here are some links to my blogs, contacts, and social media Visit my Neocities Social Media Facebook Twitter Instagram Mastadon Friendica Pixelfed Pleroma YouTube Linux For All Osint For All Peertube Contact Matrix - @the_amoghavarsha:matrix.org Email Discord - Amogh#1868 Blogs Dev Newsletter Amogh&amp;rsquo;s Tech Blog Osint Articles Critical Systems Development Github Misc Links StartMe Achievements Support Ko-fi Buy me a coffee Patreon </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/support/</guid>
      <description>Your support means a lot ❤️ 1. Ko-fi ♨️ 2. Buy me a coffee ☕ 3. Patreon 🤝 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zines</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/zines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/zines/</guid>
      <description> List of keywords in C Character sets and Tokens in C &#39;for&#39; loops &amp; don&#39;t care attitude&#39; Niche Linux commands </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
