<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:37:47 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amoghavarsha.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why Use EasyBCD When You Have GRUB</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/grub/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 05:37:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/grub/</guid>
      <description>When you set up a dual-boot system, one of the most common hurdles is managing the boot process — specifically, selecting which operating system to boot into.
This is where GRUB (Grand Unified Bootloader) steps in. If you’ve ever faced the hassle of relying on third-party tools like EasyBCD to change between operating systems, GRUB is the solution. In this article, we’ll explore how GRUB works, how it simplifies dual-booting, and some of its more advanced features that can enhance your experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Connect To WiFi Via Terminal</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/wifi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 18:43:42 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/wifi/</guid>
      <description>Do you remember the meme, which goes, &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m connecting to my WiFi using terminal, my friends&amp;hellip;HACKER&amp;rdquo;? I have never seen anyone doing that in real life. But nowadays I have a strong reason to do that in the presence or absence of my friends.
For some strange reason, my desktop environments keep breaking the much needed nm-applet. For those who may not know, generally speaking, nm-applet is the WiFi icon that you see on the top or bottom right of your screen; when clicked shows the WiFi networks available nearby.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Introduction To Web Scraping</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/web-scraping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2024 10:10:02 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/web-scraping/</guid>
      <description>I recently started seeing a lot of posts related to illegal web scarping by AI companies, all thanks to frequency illusion. In this blog, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the basics of web scraping and let&amp;rsquo;s learn how to scrape things from the web. Legality Before jumping straight into the weeds, let&amp;rsquo;s address the elephant in the room: &amp;ldquo;Is it legal to scrape the web?&amp;rdquo;. Well, it depends on who we ask this question.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ng Problem</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ng-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 23:09:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ng-problem/</guid>
      <description>Plot A few days ago, I was trying to set up an angular project. The goal was simple, that was to install angular-cli with npm or yarn. Easy-peasy.
But, the bad omen struck. Angular is a careful, robust, feature-rich framework. When I say careful, it&amp;rsquo;s very specific in many ways. The command was simple: npm install -g @angular/cli. Wanted to install angular globally, super simple, nothing crazy. Typically, it was supposed to be installed, but didn&amp;rsquo;t!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Easily Fix The Busybox/ Initramfs Error</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/busybox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 07:43:15 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/busybox/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever encountered the above error? It&amp;rsquo;s pretty annoying, innit?
Generally, it&amp;rsquo;s either called initramfs or busybox error. It typically indicates an issue during the boot process of a Linux system.
Initramfs (initial RAM file system) is a temporary file system that is loaded into memory during the boot process before the root file system is mounted. BusyBox is a set of utilities designed for embedded systems, and it is often used in initramfs environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Deploy React App On Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/react-ghpages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 21:18:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/react-ghpages/</guid>
      <description>GitHub Pages or gh-pages is one of the easiest ways to deploy static sites. But, did you know that you can also easily deploy a simple React app on GitHub Pages? Without any further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s get started.
First, install gh-pages on the React app by typing:
npm install gh-pages --save-dev Next, edit package.json by adding:
&amp;quot;homepage&amp;quot;: &amp;quot;https://yourdomain.github.io/your-react-app&amp;quot; at the top, just after { and add a couple of lines inside &amp;ldquo;scripts&amp;rdquo; object:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastodon Verification</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/mastodon-verification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 22:18:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/mastodon-verification/</guid>
      <description>Mastodon is a Twitter-like micro-blogging platform. There are a lot of tweaks that you can make on Masto, as it&amp;rsquo;s free and open-source software. It provides you with a way to verify your websites on the platform in an indie web-style way.
What Does It Mean? Imagine you have a personal blog or a website, obviously hosted on the web. So it is your online identity.
Now, let&amp;rsquo;s say, you also have other social media, and generally you would like to provide a link to your personal website or blog in the bio/description.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigating Gitignore</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/investigating-gitignore/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2023 09:51:54 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/investigating-gitignore/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago, I was working on a side project and wanted to hide a few files from Git. In the process, .gitignore caught my eye, and I started digging deeper into it. .gitignore ignores files or directories but doesn’t hide them, but how? Let’s investigate!
A .gitignore file is used to specify files or directories that should be ignored by Git when tracking changes in our project.
The purpose of .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started With Scp</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/scp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:55:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/scp/</guid>
      <description>scp is a secure way of transferring files from one computer to another. It uses ssh to transfer files, safely and securely.
In order to transfer files from one computer to another, type the following command:
scp /location/of/the/file username@ip_address_of_remote_computer:/location For example: scp ~/apple.png amogh@192.168.0.122:/amogh/home/Downloads If you want to send an entire folder, you can do that by using -r flag:
scp /location/of/the/folder username@ip_address_of_remote_computer:/location For example: scp -r ~/Downloads/MyDownloads amogh@192.168.0.122:/amogh/home/ If you have multiple ssh keys, you have to specify a particular one using -i flag:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Get Started With Tmux</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 21:55:07 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/tmux/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, let&amp;rsquo;s learn some basics of tmux, to get started right away.
What Is Tmux Tmux is a window multiplexer, which allows you to have multiple terminal sessions within a single terminal window or to detach and reattach sessions.
To install tmux, just type the following command:
sudo apt install tmux (Debian based systems) sudo pacman -S tmux (Arch based systems) sudo dnf -y install tmux (Fedora) After installation, just type tmux to get started.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Manage Multiple SSH Keys</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/multiple-ssh-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 11:21:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/multiple-ssh-keys/</guid>
      <description>In the previous article you learnt how to connect between two Linux machines, in this tutorial, you are going to learn how to manage more than one ssh keypair effectively.
In your .ssh directory, create a file called config. Inside the config add the following lines:
Host Cat HostName cat.com User amoghavarsha IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa IdentitiesOnly yes Host Dog HostName dog.com User amoghavarsha IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa.1 IdentitiesOnly yes Host * AddKeysToAgent yes IdentityFile ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pair Programming With Tmux</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/pair-programming-with-tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 02:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/pair-programming-with-tmux/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered how you can do pair programming with your friends using some simple tools?
To achieve this, you only need two things: ssh and tmux.
I&amp;rsquo;ve already explained about ssh in my other articles, you can go and check them out to get some basic understanding.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed tmux, you can do so by typing the following command (Works for Debian based systems):
sudo apt install tmux On the remote server, start a new tmux session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Connect Between Two Linux Machines</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 02:13:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ssh/</guid>
      <description>Securely connecting two computers using SSH is fairly simple and powerful. But if you are new to the world of computers, especially GNU/Linux, it could be a bit tricky to get around some basic stuff. In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you the step-by-step process to communicate between two computers using SSH.
Basics The idea is pretty simple. There are two Linux computers; let&amp;rsquo;s call them A and B. To access computer A from B (connecting to A using B&amp;rsquo;s machine), we need to place B&amp;rsquo;s public key inside A.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communities - The Good, The Bad and The Ugly</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 00:48:04 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/community/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Community: a group of people living in the same place or having a particular characteristic in common.&amp;rdquo;
 It&amp;rsquo;s a fission reaction! If we consider the whole world as a giant community and start dividing it into subgroups, there would be millions of little groups. Some call it diversity, and some call it poles. Whatever it is, we live in some kind of community, knowingly or unknowingly.
 Some communities we choose deliberately because they pique our interest, and some of them are just inevitable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzing With Good Old Radamsa</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/radamsa/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/radamsa/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;1337051nT&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;S3rlockedOSINTForall&amp;rdquo;
&amp;ldquo;oS$INTFOR@LL&amp;rdquo;
Did you know that Osint For All has many secret domain names? Just kidding, I don’t want to fuzz around any further, or maybe I do? So let’s jump in to the world of Radamsa.
Radamsa is a fuzzer. In technical terms, it is a test case generator for robustness testing. Typically, it is used to test how well a program could tolerate potentially malicious input. It works by reading files of valid data and generating random outputs every time from them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of mind-bending movies</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/non-linear/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/non-linear/</guid>
      <description>Mind-bending/non-linear/mind-twisting movies have a special place in my heart. So here’s a list of some non-linear movies that I’ve watched, those of which I can remember at the moment.
 Inception Interstellar Identity (2003) Mr. Nobody (2009) Mulholland Drive Knock at the Cabin Memento (2000) Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004) Groundhog Day Black Swan (2010) Pi (1998) The Butterfly Effect (2004) Triangle (2009) Confessions (2010) [Japanese] Donnie Darko (2001) 3-Iron (2004) [Korean] Be With You (2018) [Korean] The Man from Earth (2007) Birdman (2014) The Fountain (2006) Timecrimes (2007) [Spanish] Paprika (2006) [Anime] Mirage (2018) [Spanish] The Double (2013) Predestination (2014) Synecdoche, New York (2008) Primer (2004) Enemy (2013) Vanilla Sky (2001) Looper (2012) The Others (2001) Mother!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steganographic Tools For Beginners</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/steganography/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/steganography/</guid>
      <description>Hiding in plain sight has many dimensions. Sometimes, whatever you are looking for is before you, but you cannot see it; other times, it’s right before you but you don’t notice.
Steganography has been an art since the ancient days used to write hidden messages. It has evolved over the ages, and has changed form for the better. Nowadays we have software to hide and obfuscate messages. In this article, we’ll take a look at some amazing steganographic tools which are tiny yet powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Image Gallery</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/gallery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 18:35:46 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/gallery/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
