<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ssh on Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/tags/ssh/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ssh on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 11:21:23 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://amoghavarsha.in/tags/ssh/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Manage Multiple SSH Keys</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/multiple-ssh-keys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 11:21:23 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/multiple-ssh-keys/</guid>
      <description>In the previous article you learnt how to connect between two Linux machines, in this tutorial, you are going to learn how to manage more than one ssh keypair effectively.
In your .ssh directory, create a file called config. Inside the config add the following lines:
Host Cat HostName cat.com User amoghavarsha IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa IdentitiesOnly yes Host Dog HostName dog.com User amoghavarsha IdentityFile ~/.ssh/id_rsa.1 IdentitiesOnly yes Host * AddKeysToAgent yes IdentityFile ~/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pair Programming With Tmux</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/pair-programming-with-tmux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 02:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/pair-programming-with-tmux/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever wondered how you can do pair programming with your friends using some simple tools?
To achieve this, you only need two things: ssh and tmux.
I&amp;rsquo;ve already explained about ssh in my other articles, you can go and check them out to get some basic understanding.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t installed tmux, you can do so by typing the following command (Works for Debian based systems):
sudo apt install tmux On the remote server, start a new tmux session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Connect Between Two Linux Machines</title>
      <link>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ssh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2023 02:13:53 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://amoghavarsha.in/blogs/ssh/</guid>
      <description>Securely connecting two computers using SSH is fairly simple and powerful. But if you are new to the world of computers, especially GNU/Linux, it could be a bit tricky to get around some basic stuff. In this tutorial, I&amp;rsquo;m going to teach you the step-by-step process to communicate between two computers using SSH.
Basics The idea is pretty simple. There are two Linux computers; let&amp;rsquo;s call them A and B. To access computer A from B (connecting to A using B&amp;rsquo;s machine), we need to place B&amp;rsquo;s public key inside A.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
