<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What about about? - About page</title>
      <link>/blogs/whataboutabout/whataboutabout/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/whataboutabout/whataboutabout/</guid>
      <description>What about about? I really don&amp;rsquo;t know. Well, I&amp;rsquo;m the founder of Osint For All, I have a couple of YouTube channels that I started recently, I created this website, I watch movies/TV shows, I&amp;rsquo;m on social media, I follow some news, I do coding, I use GNU/Linux and rest you can click on other links and figure out.
But, seriously, what about having an about page? Initially I had removed my ABOUT page from this site and after some time I thought I would use this page to blog about MYSELF (subjective based on viewer&amp;rsquo;s perspective) sometimes.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;What about about? I really don&amp;rsquo;t know. Well, I&amp;rsquo;m the founder of &lt;a href=&#34;https://osintforall.in/&#34;&gt;Osint For All&lt;/a&gt;, I have a couple of YouTube channels that I started recently, I created this website, I watch movies/TV shows, I&amp;rsquo;m on social media, I follow some news, I do coding, I use GNU/Linux and rest you can click on other links and figure out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But, seriously, what about having an about page? Initially I had removed my &lt;strong&gt;ABOUT&lt;/strong&gt; page from this site and after some time I thought I would use this page to blog about &lt;strong&gt;MYSELF&lt;/strong&gt; (subjective based on viewer&amp;rsquo;s perspective) sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Maybe for you, your &lt;strong&gt;JOB&lt;/strong&gt; defines you or whatever the supreme work you do defines you, but for me, &lt;em&gt;I can just try to define myself by the end of my life&lt;/em&gt;. If I wanted  my job to define me, I had LinkedIn as a go to website, why would have I bothered to create this &lt;strong&gt;PERSONAL&lt;/strong&gt; website? On the one hand, there&amp;rsquo;s a privacy issue, on the other hand I do N number of things (apart from job) and I have many things to do in the future, so it would be an injustice if I just conform myself to a job or a particular work.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean that I don&amp;rsquo;t have a &lt;strong&gt;SPECIFIC&lt;/strong&gt; goal in life or my life is unstable; of course I have a lot of goals in life,  but haven&amp;rsquo;t you seen that motivational quote from social media, &amp;ldquo;Doing is better than saying&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Work hard in silence, let the success make noise&amp;rdquo;; that&amp;rsquo;s noice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think many of you might relate with this modern day phenomenon. Today, we have to be a 10x coder, marketer, activist, woke, hacker, husband/wife/partner, father/mother (or choose not to have a child), liberal, rich, talented, visionary, innovator, conservative, for or against Elon Musk etc., I have seen many people writing all those things on Twitter, recently I also updated few things and only I know what I mean by all those things. I wish I would have been born in the 16th century or something, so that I would have had more headspace and more time to invent and write! Or I would have also ended up as a slave, king, potter, artist, poet, singer somewhere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All this mess is because of the system that we have built, you can divide yourself politically, debating about if it&amp;rsquo;s good or bad or ugly. But the truth in the material world is, you have to be like that. Is this a new thing? Wasn&amp;rsquo;t there any competition or mental health issues in the 16th century? Of course, we had all the problems, &lt;em&gt;there could have been no present without history&lt;/em&gt; and that&amp;rsquo;s the reality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finding oneself is a life long process, we as an intelligent species (as per as our research), will possibly create a lot of problems and will also strive to find solutions to those problems and on the positive side, we&amp;rsquo;ll also create some good things in the future. And probably I will also witness all those things for some time.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/blogs/programming/programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/programming/programming/</guid>
      <description>craftsman/craftswomen is able to get their due credit, who could have their own creativity and own design. All thanks to open source and the culture that has been developed overtime. There are still some issues with psychological operations that go around reputation, but let&amp;rsquo;s hope it&amp;rsquo;ll be obsolete as we move forward.
The true ingenuity is when we write our own code. It’s a craft which can give wings to our creativity, artistic biases and solving the problem at hand.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;craftsman/craftswomen is able to get their due credit, who could have their own creativity and own design. All thanks to open source and the culture that has been developed overtime. There are still some issues with psychological operations that go around reputation, but let&amp;rsquo;s hope it&amp;rsquo;ll be obsolete as we move forward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The true ingenuity is when we write our own code. It’s a craft which can give wings to our creativity, artistic biases and solving the problem at hand. The advent of AI would probably solve or make it easier for the concerns that our left part of the brain had. Hopefully we’ll get some time to solve the problems of our right part of the brain. Or will we merge them together?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of mind-bending movies</title>
      <link>/blogs/mindbending/mindbinding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/mindbending/mindbinding/</guid>
      <description>Mind-bending/non-linear/mind-twisting movies have a special place in my heart. So here&amp;rsquo;s a list of some non-linear movies that I&amp;rsquo;ve watched, those of which I can remember.
 Inception Interstellar Identity (2003) Mr.Nobody (2009) Malholland Drive 2001: A Space Odyssey (1968) Memento (2000) Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004) Groundhog Day Black Swan (2010) Pi (1998) Shutter Island (2010) The Butterfly Effect (2004) Triangle (2009) Confessions (2010) [Japanese] Donnie Darko (2001) 3-Iron (2004) [Korean] Be With You (2018) [Korean] Fight Club The Man from Earth (2007) Source Code (2011) Birdman (2014) The Fountain (2006) Timecrimes (2007) [Spanish] Paprika (2006) [Anime] Mirage (2018) [Spanish] The Double (2013) Predestination (2014) Synecdoche, New York (2008) Primer (2004) Enemy (2013) Vanilla Sky (2001) Looper (2012) The Others (2001) Mother!</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Mind-bending/non-linear/mind-twisting movies have a special place in my heart. So here&amp;rsquo;s a list of some non-linear movies that I&amp;rsquo;ve watched, those of which I can remember.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Inception&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interstellar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identity (2003)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mr.Nobody (2009)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Malholland Drive&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2001: A Space Odyssey (1968)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Memento (2000)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Groundhog Day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Black Swan (2010)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pi (1998)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Shutter Island (2010)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Butterfly Effect (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Triangle (2009)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Confessions (2010) [Japanese]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Donnie Darko (2001)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3-Iron (2004) [Korean]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Be With You (2018) [Korean]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fight Club&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Man from Earth (2007)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source Code (2011)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Birdman (2014)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Fountain (2006)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Timecrimes (2007) [Spanish]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Paprika (2006) [Anime]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mirage (2018) [Spanish]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Double (2013)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Predestination (2014)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synecdoche, New York (2008)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Primer (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enemy (2013)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Vanilla Sky (2001)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Looper (2012)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Others (2001)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mother! (2017)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Magnolia (1999)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Machinist (2004)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A.I. Artificial Intelligence (2001)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Minority Report (2002)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Game (1997)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twelve Monkeys (1995)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Jacob&amp;rsquo;s Ladder (1990)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Gone Girl (2014)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Clockwork Orange (1971)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucia (2013) [Kannada]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Coherence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;10 Cloverfield Lane (2016)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Her&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Black Mirror: Bandersnatch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tenet&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Illusionist&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Lobster (2015)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Moon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Split (2016)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Men (2022)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Invitation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Gift&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Skin I Live In&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Rosemary’s Baby (1975)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cypher (2002)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lucy (2014)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Transcendence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Source Code&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Maanaadu (2021) [Tamil]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;No Smoking [Hindi]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;24 [Tamil]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Deja Vu (2006)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Time Machine (2002)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Dogtooth [Polish]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Sixth Sense&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Under the Skin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Irreversible [R]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Shining&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Eyes Wide Shut&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Oldboy [Korean]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Upstream Color (2013)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;ARQ (2016)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Synchronic (2019)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In the Shadow of the Moon (2019)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Signal (2014)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Knowing (2009)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Back To The Future (I,II,III)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Videodrome (1983)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact (1997)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the list continues&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have listed down the movies that I think are mind-bending or thought-provoking and I&amp;rsquo;ve excluded some (many) of them by putting them in the category of &lt;em&gt;thrillers&lt;/em&gt;. I might update this list often, so keep an eye on this post, to look inwards, maybe?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Memories of childhood..things that were lost</title>
      <link>/blogs/childhood/childhood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/childhood/childhood/</guid>
      <description>Where should I begin? Did I have the best childhood in the world? I don’t think so, but the fact that I didn’t know anything about childhood or adulthood was a solace.
“Knowing Nothing” could be a taboo in this generation. But knowing nothing and knowing that I don’t know anything is something that made me a care free child, and I loved it. But it didn’t last for a very long time, as I realized that I wanted to pass examinations to qualify for the next classes!</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Where should I begin? Did I have the best childhood in the world? I don’t think so, but the fact that I didn’t know anything about childhood or adulthood was a solace.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Knowing Nothing” could be a taboo in this generation. But knowing nothing and knowing that I don’t know anything is something that made me a care free child, and I loved it. But it didn’t last for a very long time, as I realized that I wanted to pass examinations to qualify for the next classes! Life is all about experiences, one cannot possibly control their experiences, especially when they are younger. Good, bad or ugly, you’ll only know when you grow up. Personally, for me, it was the combination of everything, and that’s interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s start from the warmth of the sun, the one that helps with the mornings, photosynthesis, and beautiful ‘sunsets’ sometimes. Getting back home after school, washing my body with cold water, and feeling a little chill and warming my legs on the balcony was fun. I barely remember someone telling me that exposing oneself to the sun is a good thing and that was my way of getting vitamin D. And I feel that it wasn’t that sunny at that time, even if the afternoons were a good time to play with friends. We barely got tired, never cared about the sweat, neither did my friends, we looked all fresh after we used to sprinkle water on our faces, and felt elated with what we all did in the break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember when I was in class two, I looked in a mirror, touched my face and had an existential question—“Who am I?” I had it a few times after that, especially in the morning when I went out to brush my teeth. Furthermore, I couldn’t find the answer and I moved on. Sometimes, I think even if I had tried a little more, my life would have been different now, I presume. Nothing’s absolute when everything is a variable in chaos.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And fast-forward to the next three years, when I saw the wind, and the cloudy evenings. I used to feel thrilled about summer evenings, especially the beginnings of the monsoon rains. I used to sleep on the terrace and enjoy the wind and the raindrops. Surprisingly, I don’t remember much about rain at that time. Maybe it was destiny.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I remember the rain a few years after that. I used to stand alone and get soaked in the rain, and run around and enjoy nature’s showers. Not only that, but I never caught a cold at that point in time. I don’t know why. Perhaps that’s how nature loved me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now, looking back on all these things, I feel that the sky is the only constant that I can relate to. I cannot find the same climate anywhere. I don’t know what spring, summer, rainy and winter seasons are anymore. It’s nice to hear the phrase “Change is the only constant in life”, but it comes with a cost, where you neither know what happened nor why it happened.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New found love</title>
      <link>/blogs/newfoundlove/newfoundlove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/newfoundlove/newfoundlove/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I started playing computer games. Well, I know they are not new to many people here, but, me being a gamer? A cold day in hell. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I can call myself a &amp;ldquo;gamer&amp;rdquo; now. Because my interests are in minimal games that range between 1-100 MB.
Prelude It was inevitable that I should have to switch to some starter GNU/Linux distributions. As there was a situation where I could not have suddenly switched to the Masterrace distros, I started to look into the distro&amp;rsquo;s software manager and then I found the category called &amp;ldquo;Games&amp;rdquo;.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I started playing computer games. Well, I know they are not new to many people here, but, me being a gamer? A cold day in hell. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I can call myself a &amp;ldquo;gamer&amp;rdquo; now. Because my interests are in minimal games that range between 1-100 MB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;prelude&#34;&gt;Prelude&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was inevitable that I should have to switch to some starter GNU/Linux distributions. As there was a situation where I could not have suddenly switched to the Masterrace distros, I started to look into the distro&amp;rsquo;s software manager and then I found the category called &amp;ldquo;Games&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friends are great gamers, but not me. The reason being I was never raised in the cradle of computers or technology. Another reason is, I just find it wasteful when a lot of GPUs&#39; energy gets sucked in by high end games. But, here we are today. The open source community makes games where I can read the source code and they are minimal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not my first time that I have gotten to the nine day wonder of gaming. I used to play some FPS games on my Linux machine, then I used to do the &amp;lsquo;silent quitting&amp;rsquo; without regrets. But this time, it&amp;rsquo;s different. I found this game called &lt;em&gt;Assult Cube&lt;/em&gt;, which is around 50 MB and it gives a decent full-fledged FPS experience!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;offshoot&#34;&gt;Offshoot&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I also found many other games (or maybe I exhausted all of them during the research) which are minimal and keep me entertaining during the break. The irony is, a break is metaphorical. Some are really addictive. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to mention every single one of them here, when you can find some really good ones that are your type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-words&#34;&gt;Final Words&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gaming is addictive. It feels like I&amp;rsquo;m going into a loop which I don&amp;rsquo;t realise when I&amp;rsquo;m in. It&amp;rsquo;s a focus inside distraction. Hypnotism has never been so real. Hope self-discretion doesn&amp;rsquo;t turn into indignation, as I can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose my new found love!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Some favorite movies</title>
      <link>/blogs/movies/movies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/movies/movies/</guid>
      <description>I am a big movie buff. Since the day I started using the computer, before diving into the internals of the computer, I’ve spent a lot of time watching movies. Maybe that’s a fractal stain in almost all Indian Engineering colleges. Even now, I love to watch movies/TV shows like the rest.
Phase 1 I don’t exactly remember what was the first foreign film that I watched. Back then, I used to have a friend who gave me a lot of English movies, such as Inception (which I watched after five years), Fight Club (which I watched lethargically), Prestige (which I watched but didn’t remember).</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;I am a big movie buff. Since the day I started using the computer, before diving into the internals of the computer, I’ve spent a lot of time watching movies. Maybe that’s a fractal stain in almost all Indian Engineering colleges. Even now, I love to watch movies/TV shows like the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;phase-1&#34;&gt;Phase 1&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t exactly remember what was the first foreign film that I watched. Back then, I used to have a friend who gave me a lot of English movies, such as Inception (which I watched after five years), Fight Club (which I watched lethargically), Prestige (which I watched but didn’t remember). I think I really got interested in cinema after watching this movie from the playlist called The Illusionist, it was a story of a magician played by Edward Norton (whom I recognized from Fight Club). I loved that movie so much back then. Not only that, but I think I watched it a couple of times and recommended to one of my other friends as well. If I remember correctly, I also watched a couple of Hindi movies that I really liked, such as Ek Villain. I’m mentioning this explicitly because watching movies on a computer without ads was a new experience for me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;phase-2&#34;&gt;Phase 2&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As I got more mature, I started watching movies with a bit more fervor. This is the phase where I started exploring the genre of non-linear movies, the Christopher Nolan type movies. I researched a lot about this genre, they were called as &lt;em&gt;mind-bending&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;mind-boggling&lt;/em&gt; or &lt;em&gt;mind twisting&lt;/em&gt; movies. Never liked to use the term non-linear, as &lt;em&gt;mind twisting&lt;/em&gt; was exciting and had a primal first best impact. In this phase, I watched almost all the English language mind twisting movies that I could find through blogs. I’m going to write a separate blog on my favorite mind-bending movies in the future. I enjoyed a lot while watching these movies, as they required me to have focus and attention to details with the hope of understanding the movie completely or near to it at the first sitting. It gave me focus and helped me to look at things differently rather than boring conventional ways. Apart from my improved observational skills, my greatest achievement is that I was able to totally indoctrinate one of my friends to this genre. Even today, they ask me recommendations for the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;phase-3&#34;&gt;Phase 3&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Like all good things must come to an end, all mind twisting movies got exhausted. Later on I jumped the ship and started watching psychological thrillers which were slightly inclined towards nonlinear genre. Till day, I’m watching them. They never bore me at all. Now my horizons have expanded as I watch a lot of foreign language films (thanks to the Internet) and OTT platforms have made them easy to access for a huge audience and that’s great. This phase was more about the contemplation of the cinemas that I had watched, I used to watch and that I might watch in the future. It was a refreshing experience when I realized that I had gained a decent amount of knowledge, perspective, and worldview through cinemas. Probably, watching cinemas for knowledge happened during Phase 2, which really made me think critically and understand the world through someone else’s lens. I should also thank a cinema website called as &lt;a href=&#34;https://thecinemaholic.com/&#34;&gt;The Cinemaholic&lt;/a&gt;, whom I used to follow daily and found a great deal of awesome recommendations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you must be curious that what phase am I currently on. Well, the answer is infinity. I’m not going to explain that to you, that’s my little secret. If you love me enough, maybe you’ll understand that one day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So what are my favorite movies? Let me tell you the top three.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0976051/?ref_=tt_mv_close&#34;&gt;The Reader&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; – Undoubtedly, it is the best movie. It made me cry. The story of love, grit, and disallowance (I understand).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0266697/&#34;&gt;Kill Bill Series&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; – It is celebrated as a revenge classic by many, but for me, it’s a story of internal conflict.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://youtube.com/watch?v=vXYB5DpqVSU&amp;amp;si=EnSIkaIECMiOmarE&#34;&gt;The Count of Monte Cristo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; - Knowledge is power and destiny favors the brave.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are still reading this and wondering where’s the Interstellar or Inception, probably you should wait for the future posts.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
