<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>recent on Amoghavarsha</title>
    <link>/tags/recent/</link>
    <description>Recent content in recent on Amoghavarsha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tags/recent/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New found love</title>
      <link>/blogs/newfoundlove/newfoundlove/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/newfoundlove/newfoundlove/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I started playing computer games. Well, I know they are not new to many people here, but, me being a gamer? A cold day in hell. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I can call myself a &amp;ldquo;gamer&amp;rdquo; now. Because my interests are in minimal games that range between 1-100 MB.
Prelude It was inevitable that I should have to switch to some starter GNU/Linux distributions. As there was a situation where I could not have suddenly switched to the Masterrace distros, I started to look into the distro&amp;rsquo;s software manager and then I found the category called &amp;ldquo;Games&amp;rdquo;.</description>
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Recently, I started playing computer games. Well, I know they are not new to many people here, but, me being a gamer? A cold day in hell. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if I can call myself a &amp;ldquo;gamer&amp;rdquo; now. Because my interests are in minimal games that range between 1-100 MB.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;prelude&#34;&gt;Prelude&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It was inevitable that I should have to switch to some starter GNU/Linux distributions. As there was a situation where I could not have suddenly switched to the Masterrace distros, I started to look into the distro&amp;rsquo;s software manager and then I found the category called &amp;ldquo;Games&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friends are great gamers, but not me. The reason being I was never raised in the cradle of computers or technology. Another reason is, I just find it wasteful when a lot of GPUs&amp;rsquo; energy gets sucked in by high end games. But, here we are today. The open source community makes games where I can read the source code and they are minimal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s not my first time that I have gotten to the nine day wonder of gaming. I used to play some FPS games on my Linux machine, then I used to do the &amp;lsquo;silent quitting&amp;rsquo; without regrets. But this time, it&amp;rsquo;s different.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;offshoot&#34;&gt;Offshoot&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I found many games (or maybe I exhausted all of them during the research) which are minimal and keep me entertaining during the break. The irony is, a break is metaphorical. Some are really addictive. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to mention every single one of them here, especially, when you can find some really good ones that are your type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;final-words&#34;&gt;Final Words&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Gaming is addictive. It feels like I&amp;rsquo;m going into a loop which I don&amp;rsquo;t realise when I&amp;rsquo;m in. It&amp;rsquo;s a focus inside distraction. Hypnotism has never been so real. Hope self-discretion doesn&amp;rsquo;t turn into indignation, as I can&amp;rsquo;t afford to lose my new found love!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
